<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title><svg class="fi fi-power" width="24px" height="24px" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><use href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/media/plugins/featherIcons/feather-sprite.svg#power" /></svg></title>
    <link href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs" />
    <updated>2025-08-19T13:17:00+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>GonzaloX41</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs</id>

    <entry>
        <title>A Philosophy of Eating Beef.</title>
        <author>
            <name>GonzaloX41</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/a-philosophy-of-eating-beef.html"/>
        <id>https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/a-philosophy-of-eating-beef.html</id>
            <category term="reflections"/>
            <category term="food and bev"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-19T13:17:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've only started to eat beef when I was 21. "Why?" you might ask. Well, partially it was religious reasons as my Mom was a buddhist. Partially, it's also I'm an actual adult, and the full&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've only started to eat beef when I was 21. "Why?" you might ask. Well, partially it was religious reasons as my Mom was a buddhist. Partially, it's also I'm an actual adult, and the full "rebelliousness" was in full effect, whereby I can think for myself without the control from a parent, piece one and one together, and make proper choices. Spoiler alert: I'm not a religious person at all (also for a future post).</p>
<p>That being said, I still remember the first time I had beef. AlaskanTF, some ex-secondary school classmates, and I went to this K-BBQ place. They were like "TRY!" looking at me with a piece of beef on their chopsticks, and they placed it on my plate. I took it, placed it in my mouth, chewed and swallowed.</p>
<blockquote><em>FUCK ME! What have I been missing all these years?</em></blockquote>
<p>I instantly fell in love with beef. The reaction of AlaskanTF and friends says it all. Ever since that day, whenever I ate out, I always selected beef as the choice of proteins, also to catch up on all the lost years of not eating beef. That soon advanced into Steakhouses. The first was <em>Jack's Place</em>, a local steakhouse. Over the few times I've been to <em>Jack's Place</em>, I tried some of the different cuts, compared to the thinly-sliced beef cuts they have in those BBQ places, it was a whole other experience. I thought <em>Jack's Place</em> was the best, <em>or so i thought</em>.</p>
<p>Cue my first overseas military exercise. On one of our off days, my superiors brought me out to <em>Texas Roadhouse</em>. I cannot remember what I had, but all I remember was the steak was the best that I had in my life, and it was my birthday as well! Up till that point, my philosophy was beef was best enjoyed as a steak. Coming back home, nowhere that sold beef here brought me the same joy as I had experienced at <em>Texas Roadhouse</em>.</p>
<p>As time went on, I stumbled upon the Omakase-style steakhouse. Just when I thought it cannot get better, it just did. These sort of steakhouses, present a Omakase Set Course menu for you, giving you different cuts of meat (though not as thick a cut compared to steaks). There <em>IS</em> actually more to just a Striploin, or a Ribeye. Don't get me wrong, while latter cuts are still enjoyable, the Omakase-style is more brilliant, as it gives you the more exotic or adventurous cuts such as Tounge, Tripe, Cheek, and so forth.</p>
<p>This is my philosophy now. Beef is best enjoyed in different cuts. I would now eagerly introduce my friends to two steakhouses locally which gives customers the Omakase Set Course menus, should we want to eat proper beef. I've grown to love Beef Tounge and Tripe. Depending on which part of the tounge it is, the tip gives you a more "bouncy" sort of profile, while the root of the tounge gives you more bite. Tripe might feel a little gamey, but if done right, it is actually quite delicious.</p>
<p>Other underrated cuts: Hanger and Skirt. These two are the more juicy cuts, with the skirt offering more of a bite.</p>
<p>Another thing I would like to mention is I have had Japanese A4 and A5 Wagyu, USDA Prime, and Australian Wagyu. Personally, Japanese A4 Wagyu is the best, as you can grill them, and eat multiple cuts, without going to the point you are sick of eating, because of all the fats and marbeling. Others are great, but Japanese A4 Wagyu is S-Tier for me.</p>
<p>That's about it.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- GonzaloX41</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Chicken Rice.</title>
        <author>
            <name>GonzaloX41</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/chicken-rice.html"/>
        <id>https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/chicken-rice.html</id>
            <category term="food and bev"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-15T14:32:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hainanese Chicken Rice - IT'S THE BEST! Where I am from, Chicken Rice could very well be a staple dish for most individuals - simple, economical, comforting and delicious. To the uninitiated, Chicken Rice very well&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hainanese Chicken Rice - IT'S THE BEST!</p>
<p>Where I am from, Chicken Rice could very well be a staple dish for most individuals - simple, economical, comforting and delicious.</p>
<p>To the uninitiated, Chicken Rice very well consists of chicken, and rice! 😁<br>But not just any rice, as the rice has to be cooked with the broth created from the chicken, with some ginger, pandan leave, and some other seasoning (one can search for the recipe online). To top it off, the chicken served could be either roasted or steamed. </p>
<p>Personally, I do not eat Chicken Rice for the chicken, I eat it for the rice, as I feel the rice is what sets apart from one stall / shop to another. Honestly, if the rice is that delicious, like from the stalls listed below, I feel I can eat an entire barrel of just the rice. In most cases, the chicken tastes similar to me (please dont sue xD). I should know better, as I have been eating this for most of my life, since childhood. And, it is for that reason, I have narrowed down to three of the best Chicken Rice stalls (in my opinion) in this country.</p>
<p>In no particular order:<br><br>1) Loy Kee Best Chicken Rice - Balestier Road<br>I'm not sure whether they changed, but the last I had, their choice of rice (looking at the length of the grains, Basmati, I presume?) absorbs the fragrance so much, such that the rice need not have the oil dressings (that come with the chicken) to go with. I also remember, they used to have Nasi Lemak as well, in which i swapped the Coconut Milk rice for Chicken Rice rice. Their chicken, is a little tough for me, and if their rice is combined with the chicken from the stalls next in this list, it is chicken rice heaven!</p>
<p>2) Feng Feng Hainanese Chicken Rice - Marsiling<br>On a good day, their rice has a balanced level of the chicken-oiliness, which creates the savoury flavour; best paired with the oil seasonings they drizzle over the chicken. Chicken is tender. Whether you are lucky or not, they also do serve achar (pickled cucumber / pineapple) to go with the meal. All in all, an excellent, economical meal.</p>
<p>3) Yishun 925 - Yishun<br>I know there are outlets other than the one in Yishun, such as one in Jurong East. They have a similar taste profile to Feng Feng, but their rice is quite consistent with the quality, oiliness level, and fluffliness, in every visit that I pay. Chicken is also soft and tender, which is bathed in the sesame oil dressing.</p>
<p>Well, there you have it. Whether you live here or whoever is visiting Singapore, and is willing to travel for good Chicken Rice, consider visiting these places that I have listed. Again, this is just my humble opinion on the best Chicken Rice spots. If you know one, you could let me know (once I figured out how to input some communication channels).<br><br></p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- GonzaloX41</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>My favourite Slasher.</title>
        <author>
            <name>GonzaloX41</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/my-favourite-slasher.html"/>
        <id>https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/my-favourite-slasher.html</id>
            <category term="random thoughts"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-11T02:11:53+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Let us start off with something borderline unhinged. We have all seen our fair share of slasher / thriller films, such as "Saw", "Scream", "Nightmare on Elm Street", "Halloween", so on and so forth. Out of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Let us start off with something borderline unhinged.</p>
<p>We have all seen our fair share of slasher / thriller films, such as "Saw", "Scream", "Nightmare on Elm Street", "Halloween", so on and so forth. Out of all of them, I would have to say Michael Myers (Halloween) is my favourite. But, really, the love for Michael Myers cemented when I was playing <em>Dead by Daylight</em> back in the day.</p>
<p>Stealth, stalk, slit - that is his killing philosophy. Simple, easy and contemporary, it gets the job done. The other killers play with their victims too much, in my opinion. In some ways, it kind of disrupts the aura and mystique around those characters.</p>
<p>Chucky: screws around too much, even though he is hard to catch and skittish (which I understand, is part of his character). This little rat somewhat gave me a somewhat traumatic lasting impression during childhood, though it is non-existent now.</p>
<p>Freddy Krueger: can't really remember much as it was plenty of years ago I watched. But I know, if one dies in the dream, he dies in real life too.</p>
<p>Jigsaw: I do not think I can survive in any of Jigsaw's games 😅</p>
<p>Jason Voorhees: never really watched Friday the 13th series. I cannot comment.</p>
<p>Ghostface: while his stealth is on-point, I can understand his thing for psychological warfare by calling his victims before killing them. Still, not my thing.</p>
<p>Which is why Michael Myers is my favourite. I would like to think I have a fighting chance against him, even though the odds are against me. I can run, but I would also expect him to walk faster than I run, or appear somewhere bamboozling me xD</p>
<p>I have watched the original 1978 film, Halloween II, and the recent reboot from 2018 to 2022. I did not really bother watching those in between, as I feel like, from the little snippets that I have watched on Youtube, it did not really bring justice to his character. Michael Myers is literally the Evil Incarnate, with an ungodly tolerance to pain. The original first two, and the recent reboot did really bring out something: the <em>fear</em>, the thriller "<em>oomph!</em>" that really brings you into the movie, and, to some extend, feeling what Michael's victims are experiencing.</p>
<p>Watching the recent and modern reboot has me rooting for both Laurie Strode and Michael Myers. Watching "Halloween Ends" was kind of a bittersweet moment. As much as I did not want this awesome franchise to end, I would still have to let go, as everything has to come an end. However, the legend behind the story of Michael Myers (and Laurie Strode, of course), will forever live. Also, the seemingly infinite amount of jumpscares when playing against Michael Myers in <em>Dead by Daylight</em>.</p>
<p>Could I also do a shoutout to the music composer behind those Halloween films I've watched - John Carpenter. As I understand, his son worked with him on the 2018 to 2022 films. How one simple melody, played with the right tempo and instrument, can be so menacing and thrilling. Just when you think they cannot outdo the original, they somehow managed to pull it off. Case in point: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m8H3M0DDWDs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Shape Hunts Allyson - John Carpenter</a>, from Halloween 2018.</p>
<p>Well, there you have it: awesome character(s), with a great aura and mystique around Michael Myers, slapping music to lift up the characters of the movie, and a beautiful thrilling energy to not make you want to look, but still take a peek to find out what happens next to the victims. This is Halloween.<br><br></p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- GonzaloX41</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pilot.</title>
        <author>
            <name>GonzaloX41</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/pilot.html"/>
        <id>https://gonzaloX41.github.io/the_memoirs/pilot.html</id>
            <category term="random thoughts"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-08T01:47:36+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    First (and test) post! This space is still bare, with just the skeleton and certain foundations being built. Nevertheless, I'd still love to thank AlaskanTF and tabsTrainee for being patient, and helping me set up this&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>First (and test) post! This space is still bare, with just the skeleton and certain foundations being built. Nevertheless, I'd still love to thank <a href="blog.alaskantf.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AlaskanTF</a> and tabsTrainee for being patient, and helping me set up this little space.</p>
<p>Hello! My name is GonzaloX41, just a random common human on this rock, made from star-dust floating through space, surviving and experiencing life. This space acts as a diary of sorts, in the case I ever suffer from Alzheimer's or Senile Dementia xD</p>
<p>I also hope to bring some form of entertainment through the day-to-day shenanigans, some thought-provoking topics, and also to share some random things that could be going through my mind. I shall try to update as and when I can.</p>
<p>Till the next post...<br><br>Warmest,<br>- GonzaloX41</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
