<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title><svg class="fi fi-power" width="24px" height="24px" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><use href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/plugins/featherIcons/feather-sprite.svg#power" /></svg></title>
    <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs" />
    <updated>2025-09-21T02:15:11+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Stephano</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Wealth Accumulation</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/wealth-accumulation-2.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/wealth-accumulation-2.html</id>
            <category term="moneytalk"/>
            <category term="09/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-09-21T01:13:49+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    DISCLAIMER: The following post contains information that is purely my thoughts and opinions. I do not represent any person, company or entity in terms of advice or equivalent. Please consult your financial consultant to discuss and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="msg msg--info">DISCLAIMER:<br>The following post contains information that is purely my thoughts and opinions. I do not represent any person, company or entity in terms of advice or equivalent. Please consult your financial consultant to discuss and plan your financial goals.</p>
<p>This post could very well be Part 2 to Insurance.</p>
<p>So, while building up on your Insurance Portfolio, another aspect that must be taken care of is Wealth Accumulation. We cannot always work for money. The trick is, make money work for you. The ultimate goal, is financial freedom. There are plenty of wealth accumulation tools -  one of which is trading in stocks (as shared in last post), if not, the following below.</p>
<h4>First Off...</h4>
<p>I would like to explain the Rule of 72. There is some link to it, as this could decide on how you would want to achieve your financial goals. Every savings instrument will give some form of interest. For you to double the amount in your savings (and not do anything to it), it will take <strong>72 Years</strong> for every 1% compounded interest per annum.</p>
<p>If a savings / investing instrument gives you 5% compounded interest per year, it will take you 14.4 years to double your amounnt. One can do the math.</p>
<h4>Where do we go from here?</h4>
<p>Again, there are different types of investment / wealth accumulation tools. One will definitely need an account for liquid assets, and probably another for illiquid assets. Chances are the illiquid assets are the one that is bringing in more interest rates. Your typical bank account gives you 0.05% interest per year, upwards to 8.05% for the High-Interest savings account (which are rather gimicky, as you have to fulfil certain criterias to achieve it).</p>
<p>Fixed deposits gives you up to 2.45%, in which you need to have a certain amount to be locked up for a certain amount of time. There are Bonds in which you can invest with the government, up to 2.5% interest per annum.</p>
<p>Besides your Life-Insurance policies, there are Endowment plans which gives you up to 4% interest, if not the Invesment-Linked Endowment plans gives you up to 8% interest, depending on performance and time horizon.</p>
<p>So you will have to ascertain your risk profile (how much risk you are willing to take), and go from there. Most people have a safer risk appetite, in which they opt in for standard Endowment plans, and let the financial institutions do its thing. The more daring ones go for higher risk tools (the higher the rewards for sure, but also, the harder the fall).</p>
<p>What I used to do was, once my pay-cheque comes in, I would pay myself (save) $1000. Next, I pay my bills, then my insurance, then the rest, for day-to-day expenditure. I live, somewhat, a frugal life. But now, with extra assets in my investment portfolio, I can spend a little more. Still, I do have a goal in mind (within the short-term), and am still working towards it.</p>
<p>In my opinion, once we have our typical bank savings account settled, I feel we can always start with an Endowment plan of sorts, as you just need to deposit a certain amount of money, rather than one lump-sum (for Fixed Deposits). If you have extra cash to spare (and are willing to lose), start investing like I do. Your endowment plan is the many layers of sponge of cake, while your riskier investment returns works as the cream or cherry on top of said cake.</p>
<p>While working towards this, it is also good to have 6 months worth of your monthly salary in your backpocket, should anything horrible happen to you. This money should not be touched as it is only for rainy days usage.</p>
<h4>Last Words...</h4>
<p>Like I mention: sit down with your financial advisor, and work out a plan to reach your financial goal. Consider the annual interest rate, time-horizon, and the amount of risk needed to be taken. Be and stay committed to the plan, and I am damn sure you could reach your goals.</p>
<p>Again, the ultimate goal, is financial freedom, where you do not need to think twice on what you spend on. We will get there... eventually.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Stock Trading.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/trading.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/trading.html</id>
            <category term="moneytalk"/>
            <category term="09/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-09-09T01:55:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    DISCLAIMER! Do not use this post as financial advice. The following information in this post is purely my comments and thoughts. Please consult your financial advisor to discuss your financial goals. Current / past performance of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>DISCLAIMER!</h3>
<p>Do not use this post as financial advice. The following information in this post is purely my comments and thoughts. Please consult your financial advisor to discuss your financial goals. Current / past performance of stocks / investment instruments are NOT indicative of future performance.</p>
<h3>Stonks!</h3>
<p>There are plenty of tools for wealth accumulation; be it endowment plans, stocks, gold, crypto, forex, so on and so forth. Right now, I'm into stock trading. I feel everyone should partake in some form of trading to, at least, accumulate some wealth on the side, besides your own month-to-month pay cheque, because relying our monthly salary or the peanut-interest rates from your bank savings account(s) are not gonna cut it.</p>
<p>Furthermore, with the advent and advancement of Aritifical Intelligence (AI), in which it could take up most of the jobs out there in future, humans will have limited ways to make money. This is why Trading is the way to go. It is kind of sad that they do not teach this in primary or secondary schools. Trading, and how to do your taxes. The government do not want the people to get rich (wearing my tinfoil hat).</p>
<h3>A little history...</h3>
<p>While studying for my Financial Consultancy license back then, we had to go through a few modules which included Trading. We had to know what the different market indexes were, what put or call options were, what going long or short were, and many other stuff. I did not really put those into practice back then, as I was quite focused on Life Insurance rather than Wealth Accumulation.</p>
<p>It was not until last year which I started Trading proper. Again, <a href="https://alaskantf.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AlaskanTF</a> came in to help refresh my memory as he had been trading for quite some time. With his expertise and rediscovering my once forgotten knowledge, I dived into Stock Trading, and trying to make the most out of it. I have financial goals that I needed to acheive by a certain time frame, and I have to say, Trading has helped me quite a bit.</p>
<p>My only two regrets were: I should have started Trading at a earlier period, and I should have invested in some crypto (Bitcoin) about ten years ago, when each coin was hovering around USD 7000 (now, it is at USD 109,000 as I type this post).</p>
<h3>What I started with...</h3>
<p>I started with some low-risk stocks, such as SP500 ETF, and Grayscale Bitcoin ETF, topped with some volatile stocks such as NVIDIA, and Palantir. Ever since then, I added more stocks into my portfolio, which covers tech, energy, defense, and the above-mentioned ETFs. I even experimented with some other stocks which did not go well; meme-stocks such as Krispy Kreme, or even Sunrun. After learning those lessons, I regrouped, and refocused on my strategy, which focused on some stocks on my portfolio.</p>
<p>While investing in stocks, whereby I have to input some money monthly, what I adopt is something called "Dollar-Cost Averaging". This is a strategy whereby you input a certain and regular amount of money, in a regular time-frame, regardless of the ups and downs of the certain index or stock. This, conversely, earns you more money, compared to buying a certain stock that keeps going up in said regular time-frame.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16/example.JPG" alt="" width="710" height="337" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16/responsive/example-xs.JPG 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16/responsive/example-sm.JPG 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16/responsive/example-md.JPG 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16/responsive/example-xl.JPG 1024w"><figcaption>How Dollar-Cost Averaging works.</figcaption></figure>
<p>As you can see, Example 2 resulted in a higher yield. This works if you are investing for the long-term. If it was a short-term investment, you will not really see results.</p>
<h3>Options</h3>
<p>Once I feel like I have gained enough wealth, I went into Option Trading to further my wealth accumulation. There are two different types of Options: a Put, and a Call.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Put Option</strong></span><br>A Put Option is some form of contact betwen you and the fund manager, whereby when the Stock hits the "strike price" of, say, $50, you, as the trader, agree to buy 1 Lot (100 Shares) of the Stock at $50. If the Stock <strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">does not</span></strong> hit the "strike price", you get to keep the money of what you sold the contract at to the fund manager. Basically, in one way or another, you are making money literally out of thin air if the Stock does not hit the "strike price".</p>
<p>The thing about Put Options though, is you <em><strong>have</strong></em> to be prepared to buy the 1 Lot at the "strike price". You have to ensure you have enough funds and liquidity in your portfolio to execute this.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Call Option</strong></span><br>This is when you already own at least 1 Lot (100 Shares) of a Stock. When you sell a Call Option, you and the fund manager have a contract whereby if the Stock hits the "strike price" of $50, you agree to sell the 100 shares at $50. If the "strike price" does not come to pass you get to keep the money of what you sold the contract at to the fund manager. However, if the "strike price" does hit, you get the money of what you sold the contract PLUS $50 x 100shares, so in totality, over $5000.</p>
<p>From the time I started Option Trading in the earlier part of this year, till now, I have made quite a good chunk of money. As I mentioned, literally making money out of thin air. Of course, it was not always a bed of roses. There are times whereby a stock I predict is going to perform positively, but it went haywire. You always learn your lessons the hard way, and try not to make the same mistake again.</p>
<h3>A final word...</h3>
<p>The picture below shows my Rate of Returns since I've started trading. Till the 30th August 2025, it is at 97.25%, with the peak being 146.54%, outperforming NASDAQ, S&amp;P500 and Dow Jones, in this time period. This is just the stocks I'm trading in, not inclusive of Options.</p>
<figure class="post__image" ><img loading="lazy" src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16//trade-2.JPG" alt="" width="766" height="396" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16//responsive/trade-2-xs.JPG 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16//responsive/trade-2-sm.JPG 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16//responsive/trade-2-md.JPG 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/16//responsive/trade-2-xl.JPG 1024w">
<figcaption >a look at the Rate of Returns thus far.</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>Of course, if you were to change the time horizon to "All-Time", the above mentioned market indexes definitely outperform me. But what I am trying to show is that Trading definitely works, if you know your stuff, and if you know what you are doing.</p>
<p>Trading, by far, to me, potentially gives me more returns to other wealth accumulation tools. The thing about Trading is, you <em><strong>have</strong></em> to be okay to lose your capital and your return of investments, as the higher the risk, the higher the rewards, also, the harder the impact, when it falls. If you dare not take the risk, stick to other safer forms of investments such as Endowment Plans, Fixed Deposits and such, in which I would be sharing about it in a future post this month (I guess this month's theme is about finance).</p>
<p>At the end of the day, do your own research on the stocks you want to trade in. The market is super volatile, especially at this time period. No one knows how the market will go, least of all, Warren Buffet or even the fund-managers. There are a lot of factors which can affect the market.</p>
<p>Once again, <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>please</strong></span> consult your Financial consultant to discuss your portfolio and financial goals. Past / Present performance of stock <strong>ARE NOT</strong> indicative of future performances.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A French Experience.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/a-french-experience.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/a-french-experience.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.50-new-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
            <category term="food and bev"/>
            <category term="adventures"/>
            <category term="09/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-09-04T10:04:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.50-new-2.jpeg" alt="" />
                    Today's post is going to be more of pictures that will do the talking. The other day, I went to a French restaurant (for the first time) for lunch, with my wine manager and some colleagues.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.50-new-2.jpeg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Today's post is going to be more of pictures that will do the talking. The other day, I went to a French restaurant (for the first time) for lunch, with my wine manager and some colleagues. It was a great experience. Excellent food, vibes, and also the wines we brought, just paired well with everything.</p>
<p>The wines we had:<br>- 2015 Louis Roederer, Cristal, Brut (Champagne, France)<br>- 2019 Domaine Jean Fery, Le Clos de Magny, Cote de Nuits-Villages (Burgundy, France)<br>- 2021 Bass Phillip, Pinot Noir, Crown Prince (Gippsland, Victoria, Australia)</p>
<p>Both the 2019 Jean Fery and 2021 Bass Phillip were meant to be a blind-tasting challenge, whereby we had to guess which was old and new world wine.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5010-2.jpeg" alt="" width="381" height="677" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5010-2-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5010-2-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5010-2-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5010-2-xl.jpeg 1024w"></figure>
<p>The restaurant is located in those old colonial buildings, and once I stepped in, I was immediately teleported to a very rustic 40s-era cottage ambience. It had somewhat of the homely feeling (refer to Featured image).</p>
<p>We started with Duck and Pork Rilettes, Cold-Cut Pork Sausage and Garlic spread, which tagged along with classic Baguette. Spread across the rilette of your choice onto your Baguette, and enjoy as it is. Delicious! The highlight of this dish is the fat, which is is oily (no doubt), but also the rich savouriness behind the mash of the meat and fat - a very rustic Burgundian-style dish. We paired this with the 2015 Cristal, and it was just perfect. The Chardonnay and Pinot Noir blend behind the champagne brought out more body (weight) from the food.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5011.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5011-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5011-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5011-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.5011-xl.jpeg 1024w"><figcaption>Left to Right: Duck Rilette, Pork Rilette, Cold Cut Pork Sausage, with Baguette to the top-left.</figcaption></figure>
<p>For Mains, we had Cote de Boeuf Angus Rotie au Four, basically a Ribeye steak, topped with caramelised onions, a Gratin and also a Duck Confit.</p>
<p>The Cote de Boeuf was beautifully done to Medium Rare, a nice balance of bite and juice. We paired this with the Pinot Noirs, and it worked better with the 2019 Jean Fery.</p>
<p>The Duck Confit had a crunchy skin, with the meat being soft and tender. The rich oiliness on the palate brought in another dimension to the taste. It was almost like Peking Duck (i think it might be an insult to Duck Confit xD please do not declare war on me).</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.504.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.504-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.504-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.504-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.504-xl.jpeg 1024w"><figcaption>Cote de Boeuf Angus Rotie au Four</figcaption></figure>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.505.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.505-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.505-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.505-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.505-xl.jpeg 1024w"><figcaption>Left: Duck Confit, Right: Gratin</figcaption></figure>
<p>Onto the wines:</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>2019 Domaine Jean Fery, Le Clos de Magny, Cote de Nuits-Villages</strong></span><br>For a wine that is about 6 years old, it was surprisingly tawny in colour, because that is usually not the case. Usually, it is more deep ruby in colour. Apparently, it had super long-maceration during the wine making process.</p>
<p>The fruit flavours were not so obvious, but there was smoke and oak profile from the wine. After 1/2-hour to about 45mins aeriating, the wine evolved super well. The fruit flavours was more obvious (there was a tinge of cola with the fruit), but the oakiness was kind of showing more compared to the fruits. An excellent pair to the medium-rare Cote de Boeuf.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>2021 Bass Phillip, Pinot Noir, Crown Prince (Australia)</strong></span><br>This wine had more of a fruit-forward profile. Not much on the oak and smoke. Youthful, bright, fresh, and a bit more on the stony profile. After opening the wine for a good 1/2-hour to 45mins, it was kind of stagnant (for me at least). I feel this is the sort of wine that is more for a stay-home drinking kind of wine.</p>
<p>Two different styles of Pinot Noir from two different countries. A lovely comparison, all in all.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.508.jpeg" alt="" width="358" height="637" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.508-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.508-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.508-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.508-xl.jpeg 1024w"></figure>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.509.jpeg" alt="" width="358" height="636" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.509-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.509-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.509-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.509-xl.jpeg 1024w"></figure>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.502.jpeg" alt="" width="361" height="642" sizes="(min-width: 760px) 660px, calc(93.18vw - 30px)" srcset="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.502-xs.jpeg 320w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.502-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.502-md.jpeg 768w ,https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/18/responsive/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-02-at-21.49.502-xl.jpeg 1024w"></figure>
<p>They decanted the wines into little chemistry beakers, which I thought it was adorable. It also works, as it has quite a wide base, and it aeriates the wine better.</p>
<p>In summary, a wonderful experience at an excellent French bistro, filled with tasty and savoury food. 5/5 for me.</p>
<p>Le Bistrot du Sommelier,<br>53 Armenian Street<br>Singapore 179940</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Insurance</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/insurance-2.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/insurance-2.html</id>
            <category term="moneytalk"/>
            <category term="09/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-09-01T13:29:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    **WARNING** Today's information in this post is strictly my thoughts and comments on today's topic. DO NOT use whatever information here as advice to further your financial portfolio. Please consult a proper Financial Consultant at your&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>**WARNING**</h3>
<p>Today's information in this post is strictly my thoughts and comments on today's topic. <strong>DO NOT</strong> use whatever information here as advice to further your financial portfolio. Please consult a proper Financial Consultant at your disposal to thoroughly discuss your financial goals.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3>Away we go~</h3>
<p>I <em>was</em> once a Financial Consultant; I no longer hold the license anymore. Still, I am an advocate for Insurance as this is some form of safety net for both you and your family, should anything happen to the breadwinner of the house. I know it works, because I am a very good example of it. Some shit happened to my family, in which I <em>might</em> discuss about it in another post, but the insurance payout helped alot, and it made sure I could stand on my own two-feet for a certain amount of time. Today we shall discuss about the different types of insurance you can find.</p>
<h3>First, a wake-up call:</h3>
<p>Correct me if I'm wrong, everyone wishes to die peacefully in their sleep. NEWSFLASH! At least half of the population will not. Somehow or rather, we may unexpectedly die in accidents or injuries. What is worse: we die slowly, suffering from diesases. If not, we may be in the hospital, put under observation for certain reasons.</p>
<p>The no.1 killer disease in humans is cardiovascular diseases, which includes the heart and lung. Next, is cancer - prostate for the men, and breast for the women. This could be hereditary, or it could be developed within oneself.</p>
<p>Long story short: all of us will die one day, regardless the cause. The question is: how do we ensure our future generations are taken care of financially?</p>
<p> </p>
<h3>The Different Types of Insurance Plans</h3>
<p>In an ideal portfolio, it is best to have all of the following covered. Even if one cannot afford to cover all at one go, it is good to slowly build up to cover every aspect of your portfolio.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Hospitalization (Intergrated Shield Plans)</strong></span><br>The most basic of all Insurance. Basically, the costs that you have incurred at your stay in your hospital, the Insurance Company will pay a good chunk of it. I do not really know how it works in other countries, but for Singapore, one has to pay the "Deductible" and "Co-Payment". The "Co-Payment" kicks in, <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>after</strong></span> he/she pays the "Deductible".</p>
<p>This should be the very first plan that you purchase, especially after you start working, as you can use your Medisave (CPF) to pay for it.</p>
<p>For example:<br>Your hospital bill: <span style="text-decoration: underline;">$100,000<br></span>Deductible: <span style="text-decoration: underline;">$3,500<br></span>Balance: <span style="text-decoration: underline;">$96,500</span><br>Co-Payment (10% of Balance): <span style="text-decoration: underline;">$9,650</span><br>You pay: <span style="text-decoration: underline;">$9,650 + $3,500 = $13,150</span><br>Insurance Company pays: <span style="text-decoration: underline;">$86,850</span></p>
<p>Depending on the Insurance companies, there is a "Rider" you can use to tag onto your Hospitalization plan, which could reduce co-payment down to a minimum of 5%, subjected to government regulations.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Whole-Life / Term-Life Plans</strong></span><br>These are insurance plans that covers you for your life. There is a difference between Whole-Life and Term. </p>
<p>After starting your career as a young-adult, this, in my opinion, should be the second plan to get for your portfolio (better if you can purchase it together with your Hospitalization plan), as the older you get, the more expensive the premium becomes, because you are more susceptible to death, as the law of nature states.</p>
<p>Whole-Life: covers you for whole of life, especially after paying all your premiums. You can purchase an X amount of "Sum Assured". Do note that the higher the "Sum Assured", the more expensive the premium is. There is an option to surrender your Whole-Life Plan, in which you receive a lump-sum payout. However, it is INADVISBLE to do so. Never use your Whole-Life plan as in investment tool, it is just not worth it.</p>
<p>Term-Life Plans: Think of it as renting a car, the moment you do not need it, you can cancel it. However, there is no option to surrender this plan to get a lump-sum payout, which makes this sort of plans a whole lot affordable compared to Whole-Life plans.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Critical Illness Plans</strong></span><br>Remember my NEWSFLASH from earlier? Again, no one is immune to diseases. For these plans, you will receive a payout should you ever (touch-wood!) contract a disease. This payout helps to cover the cost for treatment or income lost. These plans terminates itself once the payout has been given. So, if you receive the payout when you get the diesease, and you die from it, your estate will NOT get another payout from the plan.</p>
<p>However, there are options to tag Critical Illness with your Life (Whole or Term) Plans. If tagged, these plans are slightly more affordable compared to an a-la-carte purchase.</p>
<p>The mechanics for these plans differ from provider to provider. For more information on the diseases covered or mechanics of the plan, please refer to your Insurance provider.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Accident Plans</strong></span><br>These are plans that compliments your portfolio. Honestly, in my opinion, these plans are the lowest priority in today's list. For Accident Plans, you get a payout should you lose a limb, or even a part of your limb, due to accidents. I'm not really up to date about the mechanics, but there are some whereby you can get a reimbursement from your visitation to your local medical practitioner (of course, it is subjected to terms and conditions).</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Disability Income Plans</strong></span><br>Another type of Insurance that compliments your portfolio, Disability Income plans replaces a portion of your income if you are unable to work due to illness or accident (loss of limbs). Payment will stop or reduce once you start working again. </p>
<p> </p>
<h3>Last Words</h3>
<p>Once again, I am sharing whatever I know about today's topic. I hope it shed some light in the differnet types of Insurance an insurance company can provide. Do not use my information as advice. Please consult a proper Financial Consultant for your portfolio goals.</p>
<p>I believe it is a personal duty to see this aspect of life covered to ensure those that you leave behind are well taken care of, as we never know what will happen in the future. Life, is unexpectedly short. Better have it and not use it, rather than needing it when you have none.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Religion | Science</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/gods-deities-ghosts-and-demons.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/gods-deities-ghosts-and-demons.html</id>
            <category term="reflections"/>
            <category term="random thoughts"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-24T15:48:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Last post for the month. Today's post is somewhat controversial and might trigger some, but these are my thoughts and they will stay with me till I go inside a casket. I do not give a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Last post for the month. Today's post is somewhat controversial and might trigger some, but these are my thoughts and they will stay with me till I go inside a casket. I do not give a rat's ass if anyone is offended, and I will not change them. I will not take down this post as well. I'm NOT sorry.</p>
<p>In my last post, I wrote that I was not a religious man. Of course, from my childhood to teen years, it was mostly my Mom's influence on me on these matters, though during my teen years, this influence was starting to waiver as that was when I started to think for myself, making sense of the world.</p>
<p class="msg msg--success"><em>"Just like to shoot straight, I'm a man of Science." - Rick Sanchez, Rick &amp; Morty</em></p>
<p>Long story short, I do not believe in religion or supernatural entities; at the very least, until they can be studied, measured, and logged into a record of sorts. It is simple really - in science, for every electrically neutral atom, for every proton, there must be an electron. Newton's Third Law of Motion: for every action, there must be an opposite and equal reaction. If there is a good, there must be a bad. If I do not believe in one, logically, I would not believe in the other.</p>
<p>The very concept of Gods and Demons had always been a man-made thing, starting from say 50,000 to 60,000 years ago, when humans evolved some form of complexity or sophistication in our cognitive process. For example, when a volcano erupts, or it is heavily storming with thunderous roars, our forefathers would have thought the gods are angry, probably requiring a sacrifice.</p>
<p>Over the years, over time, religion has evolved into what it is today. There could have been some evidence(s) that certain individuals tied to the religions today existed, but then yet again, how credible are said evidences?</p>
<p>On the other hand, Science, consistently proves itself, remains constant, in accordance to our laws of physics, and discovers new things. In science, there is nothing to <em>believe</em>, it is whether you <em>accept</em>.</p>
<p>Today you can ask me, "what was there before nothing?"<br>I would reply, "I don't know."<br>"Then God must have created it then..."<br>So what created "God"?</p>
<p>I think when it comes to the universe, I would believe that everything was once a single super-dense object, smaller than a grain of rice, in which it exploded, expanded to what we are today. Scientists say the universe is ever expanding, some say there is a "Great Attractor" and we are heading towards it. I feel, the whole universe could be a vicious cycle. Condense into a singularity, expand, contract and condense to a singularity again.</p>
<p>Yet again, this is the beauty of science, because science has yet to tread these ever-lasting mysteries. If it ever did (and it will eventually), religion is ever a receding pocket of scientific ignorance. I think Ricky Gervais says it best, and I quote "destroy all the religious books now, in 1000 years, they will come back different. Destroy all the science books now, in 1000 years, they will still come back the same".</p>
<p>It might seem I'm bashing on religion, but these are just my reasoning as to why I'm an advocate of science. Honestly, no offense. And I can get why people need religion, as they need something to hold on to, to have faith. No right or wrong, to each his own. For me, I will face whatever as it is.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3>A Curveball</h3>
<p>Side track a little, since we are on religion and science. I have a friend that has the "third eye", meaning she can see, experience and interact with supernatural beings, good or bad. We call her the "Ghost Hunter".</p>
<p>Again, I do not believe in these stuffs, but when it comes to her, I will not label her as a "schizophrenic" because it does not make sense to do so, and it is low-key offensive to just dismiss her experiences. She is a very good friend for years, and she has no reason to lie. When it comes to this, at best, I am a skeptic. I believe in her beliefs of these experiences. Again, I will fully believe when these entities can be measured in one way or another.</p>
<p>Maybe, let's just say these entities exists: what if she is one of those who can tap into a higher dimension to interact with these entities? What if these entities exist in a dimension that is beyond our own (3 dimensions that of space, 1 of time). What if this is the next step in human evolution, to transcend time to whenever we want (something like in the movie <em>Interstellar</em>)?</p>
<p>Just a little something to ponder.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A Philosophy of Eating Beef.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/a-philosophy-of-eating-beef.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/a-philosophy-of-eating-beef.html</id>
            <category term="reflections"/>
            <category term="food and bev"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-19T13:17:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've only started to eat beef when I was 21. "Why?" you might ask. Well, partially it was religious reasons as my Mom was a buddhist. Partially, it's also I'm an actual adult, and the full&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've only started to eat beef when I was 21. "Why?" you might ask. Well, partially it was religious reasons as my Mom was a buddhist. Partially, it's also I'm an actual adult, and the full "rebelliousness" was in full effect, whereby I can think for myself without the control from a parent, piece one and one together, and make proper choices. Spoiler alert: I'm not a religious person at all (also for a future post).</p>
<p>That being said, I still remember the first time I had beef. AlaskanTF, some ex-secondary school classmates, and I went to this K-BBQ place. They were like "TRY!" looking at me with a piece of beef on their chopsticks, and they placed it on my plate. I took it, placed it in my mouth, chewed and swallowed.</p>
<blockquote><em>FUCK ME! What have I been missing all these years?</em></blockquote>
<p>I instantly fell in love with beef. The reaction of AlaskanTF and friends says it all. Ever since that day, whenever I ate out, I always selected beef as the choice of proteins, also to catch up on all the lost years of not eating beef. That soon advanced into Steakhouses. The first was <em>Jack's Place</em>, a local steakhouse. Over the few times I've been to <em>Jack's Place</em>, I tried some of the different cuts, compared to the thinly-sliced beef cuts they have in those BBQ places, it was a whole other experience. I thought <em>Jack's Place</em> was the best, <em>or so i thought</em>.</p>
<p>Cue my first overseas military exercise. On one of our off days, my superiors brought me out to <em>Texas Roadhouse</em>. I cannot remember what I had, but all I remember was the steak was the best that I had in my life, and it was my birthday as well! Up till that point, my philosophy was beef was best enjoyed as a steak. Coming back home, nowhere that sold beef here brought me the same joy as I had experienced at <em>Texas Roadhouse</em>.</p>
<p>As time went on, I stumbled upon the Omakase-style steakhouse. Just when I thought it cannot get better, it just did. These sort of steakhouses, present a Omakase Set Course menu for you, giving you different cuts of meat (though not as thick a cut compared to steaks). There <em>IS</em> actually more to just a Striploin, or a Ribeye. Don't get me wrong, while latter cuts are still enjoyable, the Omakase-style is more brilliant, as it gives you the more exotic or adventurous cuts such as Tounge, Tripe, Cheek, and so forth.</p>
<p>This is my philosophy now. Beef is best enjoyed in different cuts. I would now eagerly introduce my friends to two steakhouses locally which gives customers the Omakase Set Course menus, should we want to eat proper beef. I've grown to love Beef Tounge and Tripe. Depending on which part of the tounge it is, the tip gives you a more "bouncy" sort of profile, while the root of the tounge gives you more bite. Tripe might feel a little gamey, but if done right, it is actually quite delicious.</p>
<p>Other underrated cuts: Hanger and Skirt. These two are the more juicy cuts, with the skirt offering more of a bite.</p>
<p>Another thing I would like to mention is I have had Japanese A4 and A5 Wagyu, USDA Prime, and Australian Wagyu. Personally, Japanese A4 Wagyu is the best, as you can grill them, and eat multiple cuts, without going to the point you are sick of eating, because of all the fats and marbeling. Others are great, but Japanese A4 Wagyu is S-Tier for me.</p>
<p>That's about it.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Chicken Rice.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/chicken-rice.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/chicken-rice.html</id>
            <category term="food and bev"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-15T14:32:00+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hainanese Chicken Rice - IT'S THE BEST! Where I am from, Chicken Rice could very well be a staple dish for most individuals - simple, economical, comforting and delicious. To the uninitiated, Chicken Rice very well&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hainanese Chicken Rice - IT'S THE BEST!</p>
<p>Where I am from, Chicken Rice could very well be a staple dish for most individuals - simple, economical, comforting and delicious.</p>
<p>To the uninitiated, Chicken Rice very well consists of chicken, and rice! 😁<br>But not just any rice, as the rice has to be cooked with the broth created from the chicken, with some ginger, pandan leave, and some other seasoning (one can search for the recipe online). To top it off, the chicken served could be either roasted or steamed. </p>
<p>Personally, I do not eat Chicken Rice for the chicken, I eat it for the rice, as I feel the rice is what sets apart from one stall / shop to another. Honestly, if the rice is that delicious, like from the stalls listed below, I feel I can eat an entire barrel of just the rice. In most cases, the chicken tastes similar to me (please dont sue xD). I should know better, as I have been eating this for most of my life, since childhood. And, it is for that reason, I have narrowed down to three of the best Chicken Rice stalls (in my opinion) in this country.</p>
<p>In no particular order:<br><br>1) Loy Kee Best Chicken Rice - Balestier Road<br>I'm not sure whether they changed, but the last I had, their choice of rice (looking at the length of the grains, Basmati, I presume?) absorbs the fragrance so much, such that the rice need not have the oil dressings (that come with the chicken) to go with. I also remember, they used to have Nasi Lemak as well, in which i swapped the Coconut Milk rice for Chicken Rice rice. Their chicken, is a little tough for me, and if their rice is combined with the chicken from the stalls next in this list, it is chicken rice heaven!</p>
<p>2) Feng Feng Hainanese Chicken Rice - Marsiling<br>On a good day, their rice has a balanced level of the chicken-oiliness, which creates the savoury flavour; best paired with the oil seasonings they drizzle over the chicken. Chicken is tender. Whether you are lucky or not, they also do serve achar (pickled cucumber / pineapple) to go with the meal. All in all, an excellent, economical meal.</p>
<p>3) Yishun 925 - Yishun<br>I know there are outlets other than the one in Yishun, such as one in Jurong East. They have a similar taste profile to Feng Feng, but their rice is quite consistent with the quality, oiliness level, and fluffliness, in every visit that I pay. Chicken is also soft and tender, which is bathed in the sesame oil dressing.</p>
<p>Well, there you have it. Whether you live here or whoever is visiting Singapore, and is willing to travel for good Chicken Rice, consider visiting these places that I have listed. Again, this is just my humble opinion on the best Chicken Rice spots. If you know one, you could let me know (once I figured out how to input some communication channels).<br><br></p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>My favourite Slasher.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/my-favourite-slasher.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/my-favourite-slasher.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/7/bgf8f8f8-flat750x075f-pad750x1000f8f8f8.u1.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="random thoughts"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-11T02:11:53+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/7/bgf8f8f8-flat750x075f-pad750x1000f8f8f8.u1.jpg" alt="" />
                    Let us start off with something borderline unhinged. We have all seen our fair share of slasher / thriller films, such as "Saw", "Scream", "Nightmare on Elm Street", "Halloween", so on and so forth. Out of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/media/posts/7/bgf8f8f8-flat750x075f-pad750x1000f8f8f8.u1.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Let us start off with something borderline unhinged.</p>
<p>We have all seen our fair share of slasher / thriller films, such as "Saw", "Scream", "Nightmare on Elm Street", "Halloween", so on and so forth. Out of all of them, I would have to say Michael Myers (Halloween) is my favourite. But, really, the love for Michael Myers cemented when I was playing <em>Dead by Daylight</em> back in the day.</p>
<p>Stealth, stalk, slit - that is his killing philosophy. Simple, easy and contemporary, it gets the job done. The other killers play with their victims too much, in my opinion. In some ways, it kind of disrupts the aura and mystique around those characters.</p>
<p>Chucky: screws around too much, even though he is hard to catch and skittish (which I understand, is part of his character). This little rat somewhat gave me a somewhat traumatic lasting impression during childhood, though it is non-existent now.</p>
<p>Freddy Krueger: can't really remember much as it was plenty of years ago I watched. But I know, if one dies in the dream, he dies in real life too.</p>
<p>Jigsaw: I do not think I can survive in any of Jigsaw's games 😅</p>
<p>Jason Voorhees: never really watched Friday the 13th series. I cannot comment.</p>
<p>Ghostface: while his stealth is on-point, I can understand his thing for psychological warfare by calling his victims before killing them. Still, not my thing.</p>
<p>Which is why Michael Myers is my favourite. I would like to think I have a fighting chance against him, even though the odds are against me. I can run, but I would also expect him to walk faster than I run, or appear somewhere bamboozling me xD</p>
<p>I have watched the original 1978 film, Halloween II, and the recent reboot from 2018 to 2022. I did not really bother watching those in between, as I feel like, from the little snippets that I have watched on Youtube, it did not really bring justice to his character. Michael Myers is literally the Evil Incarnate, with an ungodly tolerance to pain. The original first two, and the recent reboot did really bring out something: the <em>fear</em>, the thriller "<em>oomph!</em>" that really brings you into the movie, and, to some extend, feeling what Michael's victims are experiencing.</p>
<p>Watching the recent and modern reboot has me rooting for both Laurie Strode and Michael Myers. Watching "Halloween Ends" was kind of a bittersweet moment. As much as I did not want this awesome franchise to end, I would still have to let go, as everything has to come an end. However, the legend behind the story of Michael Myers (and Laurie Strode, of course), will forever live. Also, the seemingly infinite amount of jumpscares when playing against Michael Myers in <em>Dead by Daylight</em>.</p>
<p>Could I also do a shoutout to the music composer behind those Halloween films I've watched - John Carpenter. As I understand, his son worked with him on the 2018 to 2022 films. How one simple melody, played with the right tempo and instrument, can be so menacing and thrilling. Just when you think they cannot outdo the original, they somehow managed to pull it off. Case in point: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m8H3M0DDWDs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Shape Hunts Allyson - John Carpenter</a>, from Halloween 2018.</p>
<p>Well, there you have it: awesome character(s), with a great aura and mystique around Michael Myers, slapping music to lift up the characters of the movie, and a beautiful thrilling energy to not make you want to look, but still take a peek to find out what happens next to the victims. This is Halloween.<br><br></p>
<p>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pilot.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stephano</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/pilot.html"/>
        <id>https://LCStephano.github.io/the_memoirs/pilot.html</id>
            <category term="pilot"/>
            <category term="08/2025"/>

        <updated>2025-08-08T01:47:36+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    First (and test) post! This space is still bare, with just the skeleton and certain foundations being built. Nevertheless, I'd still love to thank AlaskanTF and tabsTrainee for being patient, and helping me set up this&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>First (and test) post! This space is still bare, with just the skeleton and certain foundations being built. Nevertheless, I'd still love to thank <a href="blog.alaskantf.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AlaskanTF</a> and tabsTrainee for being patient, and helping me set up this little space.</p>
<p>Hello! My name is Stephano. The 'LC' in the link just stands for LeCreuset. I'm just a random regular human, just like you, on this rock we call "Earth", made from star-dust floating through space, surviving and experiencing life. This space acts as a diary of sorts, in the case I ever suffer from Alzheimer's or Senile Dementia xD</p>
<p>I also hope to bring some form of entertainment through the day-to-day shenanigans, some thought-provoking topics, and also to share some random things that could be going through my mind. I shall try to update as and when I can.</p>
<p>Till the next post...<br><br>Warmest,<br>- Stephano</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
